Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Good evening, everyone.
Thanks
be to Almighty God, we have another
opportunity
to join here together in our fellowship.
Thanks be to God.
So brothers and sisters,
tonight, we've got another wonderful
topic to share
with each and every single one of you.
Because we are going to talk about the
mystery of God's judgment work in the last days
Yeah, does anyone know what the judgment
is all about?
Have you ever heard about God's work of
judgment?
How it will be fulfilled?
Does anyone know how the judgment will be
fulfilled in the last days?
Yes, brothers and sisters.
Brothers and sisters?
Probably not, right?
Well, you can you can let me know.
You can let me know in the group chat.
How do you think the judgment is going to
be fulfilled?
Or maybe your church doesn't talk about
it, right?
That's okay.
Because that's going to be our topic here
for tonight.
Okay, brothers and sisters, that's going
to be our topic here for tonight.
And I think you're going to enjoy it.
Because you know, judgment really relates to our entry into the kingdom of heaven.
you know
if we don't have judgment brothers and sisters
if we don't experience God's judgment work
then you already know, we cannot enter the kingdom of heaven
so, I pray, I pray each and single one of us can give our undivided attention
Alright? So let us quiet our hearts, brothers and
sisters.
And let's come together in prayer.
All right, let's quiet our hearts.
And let's pray.
Let's pray.
Dear Heavenly Father, Almighty God,
dear Lord, I just pray that you quiet each
and every single one of our hearts,
dear God, as we come together in prayer.
And in time of fellowship, dear God,
we're so thankful that we have this
opportunity to join in hand in hands with
your truth, dear God, and to learn about
the work that you come back to do in the
last days, which is the judgment work.
Many of us may not understand why.
Why do you need to come back?
Why do you need to come back to carry out
the work of judgment?
You
see, this work of judgment, dear God, it
relates
to all of us, to all of us that are here.
And this is
an incredible work that you come back to do
as the Son of Man
in order to prepare us for your kingdom.
So I pray that we can give our undivided
attention to your truth, dear Lord.
I hope that you can lead and guide each
and every single one of our hearts,
dear Lord.
And may we come together in true worship,
true fellowship.
With you, dear God.
May we cooperate with you right now so
that we may understand your work.
I also
pray for many brothers and sisters here who
are going
through many difficulties in their life.
Dear God, I pray that you also be with
them.
Even though they're going through many
trials, they still take their time to be
here and to dedicate this precious time
with you, dear God.
It goes to show that their heart really is
with you.
And that's exactly what you approved.
And we thank you.
We thank you wholeheartedly.
So dear God, as we come together,
we just pray that our hearts can be quiet.
But we can just spare this an hour and a
half in our true worship for you.
And may you work in our hearts,
dear God.
May you work in our spirits as well.
May you give us
understanding of the judgment work so that
we can be more
prepared in order to welcome your return.
We just want
to give you all the praise, all the honor,
and all the glory
in your precious, righteous, holy name.
Jesus Christ, we pray.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
All right.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So yes, let's get started.
Let's get started, everyone.
I hope you will enjoy.
Okay, I hope you will enjoy tonight's
topic as much as me because, you know,
brothers
and sisters, the reason why we all join
is because,
you know, we really want to understand.
Amen, Sister Emma.
We really want to understand God's work in
the last days.
You know, we've all been believers for
many years.
And we know that one
of our greatest hope one of our greatest
blessings is to really
be caught up into the kingdom of heaven.
But we have
to understand that the key to efficiency
So, achieving
this is welcoming the Lord's return.
And last night,
brothers and sisters, we fellowshiped
about God becoming
flesh a second time as the Son of Man.
And you see, there are some people who ask
me, Sister Thelma, why can't the Lord
simply take us directly into the kingdom
of heaven?
Why become flesh again?
Well, when the Lord returns, brothers and
sisters, he's got work to do, right?
He's got work to do, my dear brothers and
sisters.
Does anyone know what work is prophesied
over 200 times in the Bible?
What work is prophesied over 200 times in
the Bible?
Does anyone know?
I'll tell you.
The work that is prophesied over 200 times
in the Bible...
It is the judgment work.
Amen, Brother Edgar?
It is
actually mentioned over 200 times, and it's
directly
tied to us entering the kingdom of heaven.
Let's take a look at some Bible verses so
you understand what I mean, okay?
I'm not going to send you 200 of
them, but I'll send you some of them, okay?
200 is a lot to go through, but we can
talk, we can look over some.
The first one is, for the time has come that
judgment must begin at the house of God.
First Peter 4, 17.
Then we have, for the Father judges no
man, but has committed all judgment to the
Son,
and has given him authority to execute
judgment
also, because he is the Son of Man.
John 5, 22 to 27.
And if any man hears my words and believes
not, I judge him not.
For, I came not to judge the world,
but to save the world.
He that rejects me, and accepts not my
words, has one that judges him.
The word that I have spoken, the same
shall judge him in the last day.
John 12, 47 to 48.
I have yet many things to say to you,
but you cannot bear them now.
However, when he, the Spirit of truth,
has come, he will guide you into all truth.
John 16, 12 to 13.
For he comes to judge the world,
but he does not judge the world.
He does not judge the world, but he does
not judge the earth.
With righteousness shall he judge the
world, and the people with justice.
Psalm 98, 9.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So, the Lord did prophesy that he would
come back as the Son of Man in the last
days to do what?
Welcome, Sister Miriam, to express the
truth and to carry out the work of judgment.
But
brothers and sisters, do you think this
work
of judgment is just for the non-believers?
What do you think?
You think this work is only for the
non-believers, brothers and sisters?
Yes or no?
God doing the work of judgment,
is it only for the non-believers?
Take a look what the Bible says,
right?
1 Peter 4, 17.
Amen, Jasmine and Edgar, right?
If
you pay attention, it says, for the time is
come that
judgment must begin at the house of God.
1 Peter 4, 17.
Now, you need to ask yourselves,
right?
Ask yourselves, brothers and sisters,
who lives in the house of God?
Is it the believers or the non-believers?
Who lives in the house of God?
Would you say believers or non-believers?
Hmm.
Believers or non-believers?
Who lives in the house of God?
And the answer is, it is obviously,
that's right, it's obviously the believers.
Yes, brothers and sisters, it is the
believers that lives in the house of God.
So judgment begins with us, the believers,
not the non-believers, okay?
And I know some of you may be confused,
thinking, well, we as believers,
aren't our sins forgiven already?
So when the Lord comes back, shouldn't he
just take us up into the kingdom of heaven?
You see,
a lot of people may not understand, why
does
judgment have to begin at the house of God?
Why do we believers have to go through the
work of judgment?
This is a critical issue, isn't it?
But
let me tell you, it's directly tied to our
salvation and
to our entry into the kingdom of heaven.
Now, if we don't understand the
significance of God's judgment work,
then we'll just miss our chance to welcome
the Lord.
We'll miss our chance to be caught up.
So let's dive in, okay, brothers and
sisters?
Let's dive in.
Because if we want to understand why God
carries out the work of judgment,
welcome
Charles, welcome Lindsay, we first need to
know exactly
who can enter the kingdom of heaven?
Welcome Nicholas.
Who can enter the kingdom of heaven, brothers and
sisters.
There are
so many people who will say, well, our sins
are forgiven,
so we can go into the kingdom of heaven.
As long as we read the Bible, as long as
we pray, as long as we do good deeds,
the Lord will take us up into the kingdom
of heaven when he returns.
But is that correct, brothers and sisters?
To enter the kingdom of heaven,
we need to know the conditions.
You tell me, who gets to decide whether we
go to God's kingdom?
You think it's anyone?
What do you think brothers and sisters?
Who gets to decide of who can enter the
Kingdom of Heaven?
Is it anyone?
Is it anyone who gets to decide?
What do you think?
Neve says only God.
Anyone else brothers and sisters?
Yeah, feel free to feel free to type okay.
Who do you think gets to decide?
Who gets to decide?
Is it anyone?
Who is it?
That's right brothers and sisters.
I think we can all agree when we say only
Christ.
Right?
Only Jesus.
Only the Son of Man has the final say.
That's right brothers and sisters.
Remember, he's the one that holds the key
to the Kingdom.
You can't get to the Father unless you go
through him.
After all, his words are the truth,
the way, and the life.
So let's see what the Lord Jesus said
about who can enter the Kingdom of Heaven.
Okay brothers and sisters, let's follow
along.
Let's find what are the conditions of
entering the Kingdom of Heaven.
Because the Lord is very clear.
Very clear.
All right, here we go.
Amen, Rose.
Amen.
You see, there are conditions for us to
enter the Kingdom of Heaven.
You see, the Lord Jesus said,
Not every one that saith unto me, Lord, Lord, shall enter into the kingdom of heaven;
but he that doeth the will of my Father which is in heaven
Many will say to Me in that day, Lord, Lord, have we not prophesied in Your name
and in Your name have cast out devils
and in Your name done many wonderful works?
And then will I profess to them, I never knew you: depart from Me
you that work iniquity
Matthew 7, 21 to 23.
The Lord Jesus also said.
Truly, truly, I say to you
Whoever commits sin is the servant of sin.
And the servant stays not in the house for ever: but the son stays ever
John 8:34-35
You see, based on the Lord's words,
not everyone who believes and keeps the
Lord's name can actually enter the kingdom
of heaven.
But do you know who?
Who can?
Welcome, Colby.
You know who can, brothers and sisters?
He that follows the will of my Father,
which is in heaven.
And what does doing the heavenly Father's
will actually mean?
Well, the Lord Jesus did say, whoever
commits sin is the servant of sin.
And the servant stays not in the house
forever, but the son stays ever.
Do you see, brothers and sisters?
Do you see?
It is only those who completely break free
from sin can enter the kingdom of heaven.
So now, what does it mean to do the
Father's will?
Doing the heavenly Father's will,
it means we need to stop sinning,
we need to stop opposing God, and we need
to put the Lord's words into practice.
Alright?
We need to put the Lord's words into
practice.
Let's look at two more verses,
brothers and sisters.
Two more verses, right?
It says, You shall therefore be holy,
for I am holy.
Leviticus 11.45 Without holiness,
no man shall see the Lord.
Hebrews 12.14 Did anyone
notice something?
Did you notice the key word in these two
verses, brothers and sisters?
Did anyone notice?
What are the key words in these two Bible
verses?
What are the key words?
Brothers and sisters.
Exactly, Brother Edgar.
Brothers and sisters, the key words is the
fact that you've got to be holy.
To enter the kingdom of heaven,
you've got to achieve holiness.
You have to break free from sin and be
completely cleansed.
That's the only standard to get in.
Look at the conditions.
The conditions for entering the kingdom of
heaven, stop sinning, achieve holiness,
live by the word of God, and completely
obey God.
That's what it is, brothers and sisters,
okay?
Summing it up, you've got to stop sinning.
You've got to achieve holiness.
You've got to live according to the word
of God.
And you've got to completely submit to
God.
Now let me ask you all an honest question.
Are we holy right now?
Do we meet the standard, brothers and
sisters?
What do you think?
Do we meet the standard?
This is a time where we can start being,
you know, layering, laying our hearts bare.
Do you think you're holy?
Right now?
Colby?
Monica?
You think you're holy?
Akun?
What about Rose?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Cunningham?
You think you're holy?
Edgar says no.
Colby says no.
I also say no, by the way.
Anyone else?
Rose says I'm trying.
May says no.
You can type, Sister Annie.
Monica says no.
Jasmine says no.
May says no.
Kenneth says no.
Alex says no.
Neve says no.
Brothers and sisters, yeah.
None of us are.
We have not yet met God's standard in
becoming a holy person.
Let's take an honest look at ourselves,
okay?
Should we be honest right now?
Because aren't we always committing these
sins to some degree?
I'll tell you some of the sins that many
of us commit, okay?
Maybe that's you, maybe that's not you.
You can either say, yes, you could say,
no, or you can just listen.
Right?
Here we go, brothers and sisters.
So, the Lord Jesus teaches us to be
honest.
But, don't we still often lie,
just to save our face or, out of vanity?
The Lord also, number two.
The Lord teaches us to be tolerant and
patient.
But, when things don't go your way,
we're just as patient.
But, if things Don't go our way.
Don't we still lose our temper?
Or what about three?
When we see others doing better than us,
don't we still get jealous?
And number four, when many people go to
church just to get grace and blessings,
but don't care at all about the Lord's
teachings and fail to practice this...
How many people, sorry, how many people
still go to church, right?
Just to get grace and blessings,
but don't care at all about the Lord's
teaching, and they even fail to practice
His words?
That's a lot of people, don't you think,
brothers and sisters?
Don't you think?
A lot, right?
Amen, my dear sister Monica.
A lot, brothers and sisters.
In fact, many people admit that we still
commit sins.
We fight for fame and gain.
We argue out of jealousy.
We follow evil trends of the world.
Many people worship money and status.
And on top of that, we attack and judge
one another.
We lie.
Hey, the list goes on.
Every single one of us is stuck in the
cycle of sinning and confessing.
We lie
during the day, then we pray and confess
at
night, promising we'll never do it again.
But the very next hour or the very next
day, we just can't help ourselves.
We end up telling even more lies.
And on top of that, we still resist God.
You see, when things are peaceful, we're
quick to praise the Lord with our lips.
But the moment disasters strike,
we start complaining.
When God does something that doesn't line
up with our own ideas, we doubt Him.
We distance ourselves from Him,
and we even condemn Him.
Now, isn't that betraying and resisting
God?
It is.
So even though our sins are forgiven,
we're still filthy and corrupt.
Look at the picture I sent you,
brothers and sisters.
We still have all of these.
In terms of our corrupt essence,
we're still completely hostile to God.
We're still arrogant, deceitful,
greedy, lustful, jealousy, vanity,
pride, stubbornness, you name it.
So having our sins forgiven does not mean
that we have stopped sinning.
It doesn't mean that we're holy.
It doesn't mean that we can actually
submit to God in all things.
And it definitely does not mean that we
can follow God's will.
You see, we've
believed in the Lord for years, but we're
still stuck
in the cycle of sinning and confessing.
Now you tell me, brothers and sisters,
because we're still stuck in the cycle of
sinning and confessing, can we enter God's
kingdom right now?
What do you think?
Would you say yes?
That we can enter God's kingdom right now?
Yes or no?
Exactly, brother Edgar.
Amen, sister Monica.
Amen, my dear sister.
Brothers and sisters, absolutely not.
Amen, Neves.
Absolutely not.
You see, right now, we cannot enter the
kingdom of heaven.
The kingdom of heaven is absolutely
closed.
It's locked up.
Because at the end of the day,
what do we do?
All we do is love.
We love waving the banner of, I'm forgiven
by the blood of the lamb.
I'm forgiven by the blood of the lamb.
We love using those words.
The blood of Jesus forgave me.
The blood of Jesus did that for me.
But yet you're still rejecting Jesus.
You can't enter the kingdom of heaven like
that.
You
see, the kingdom of heaven, brothers and
sisters, it
is only opened to those who are cleansed.
Us who still live in sin.
Us who still enjoy the pleasures of sin.
Yet we still expect to be taken into the
kingdom of heaven.
That's just daydreaming.
Welcome, sister Kim.
That's daydreaming, brothers and sisters.
Did we all forget?
God is holy.
How could he allow filthy people into his
kingdom?
You see, no matter how many years we've
believed in the Lord, as long as we're
living in sin, we're not qualified to
enter the kingdom of heaven.
That's for sure.
It's completely determined by God's
righteous disposition and his holy essence.
You see, brothers and sisters?
Now, let's take a moment to answer this
question together, okay?
Let's take a moment to answer this
question together.
Sister
Annie, we mainly focus on how to welcome
the
Lord's second coming, my dear sister.
We're preparing for the Lord's return,
okay?
That's what's important right now,
my dear sis.
But I don't know anything about that,
to be honest, Sister Annie.
I don't know anything about that.
So take a moment, brothers and sisters.
Welcome, Brother Mark.
Brothers and sisters, what do you think?
Since we have believed in the Lord Jesus
for years and our sins are forgiven,
are we qualified to directly enter God's
kingdom?
A, no, because we can still sin and have
not achieved holiness.
Or B, yes.
We can, because our sins are forgiven.
We can directly enter into the kingdom of
heaven.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Amen, Sister Rose.
Amen, Brother Edgar.
Amen, Brother Colby.
Amen, Kenneth.
Actually, brothers and sisters,
the answer is no.
Just
because... Amen, Sister Annette.
That's right, Sister.
So, Sister May, the correct answer is
actually A.
All right?
We're not qualified to enter the kingdom
of heaven directly, brothers and sisters.
You have to understand, if that was the
case, everybody would be there right now.
Everybody would be there.
Yes, we're forgiven, but remember, we're
still committing sins every single day.
Now, if God were to put each and every
single one of us into his kingdom,
we would still be sinning in his kingdom.
What, you
think God is going to, you know, make you
perfect by
the blink of an eye or a snap of a finger?
No, absolutely not.
God still needs to teach you the truth.
He still needs to teach you how to act
holy, how to be righteous.
Because if we were taken to the kingdom of
heaven right now, boy oh boy, poor God,
right?
Because we would still be sinning up
there.
We would still be sinning, and that's not
okay.
And I don't want us to feel discouraged,
okay?
Because, yeah, we know
no one is holy right now, but remember,
entering the
kingdom of heaven has always been a sin.
God's promise to mankind.
Remember what did God say?
You shall therefore be holy, for I am
holy.
So there's definitely a way to achieve
holiness.
So us sharing this truth tonight is to
help everyone understand the conditions
for entering the kingdom of heaven, so
we can all find a path to get there, okay?
That's exactly what we're talking about
right now, brothers and sisters.
Finding a path to achieve holiness and to
enter the kingdom of heaven.
All right, brothers and sisters?
Everyone clear so far?
You clear so far?
I can't wait.
A-Land Sisternet.
Yes, stay until the end, brothers and
sisters, and we will find a path to get there.
I promise.
I promise, okay?
You got to stay until the very end,
because we will find a path to get there.
But we'll go step by step so we can
understand the full picture.
You see, because a lot of people,
they wonder, they wonder.
They say, since the Lord Jesus was
crucified for our sins 2000 years ago,
why are we still stuck in this cycle of
sinning and confessing?
Why can't we break free from the bondage
of sin?
Why?
Well, to figure this out, we need to understand
exactly what work the Lord Jesus did.
If you want to know why you can't break free from the bondage of sin
it is because you need to understand what did the Lord Jesus do and
what he didn't do.
You also need to understand the background
of his work at that time.
And let me give you a rundown.
You see, in the beginning, God issued the
laws and the commandment to teach people
how to live on earth.
You see, he told them not to kill, not to
steal, not to commit adultery, and so on.
You see,
these laws made it very clear to people
what
they should and what they shouldn't do.
They taught people right from wrong.
By issuing these laws, God showed people
exactly what sin was.
Anyone who broke the law, they got
punished accordingly of course
and I'll give you an
example, right?
If
you broke the law, you would either be
stoned
to death or burned by Jehovah's fire.
Yeah, stoned to death or burned by
Jehovah's fire from heaven.
You see, at the same time, God was showing
mercy.
So to avoid being condemned by the law,
people had to make sin offerings,
such as an unblemished ox or sheep.
However, because of Satan's corruption,
people often couldn't keep the law anymore.
And towards the end of the age of law,
people were sinning so much that they
actually ended up running out of sin
offering.
And remember,
without a sin offering, many people
were faced
being condemned or put to death by the law.
And that's when the Lord Jesus personally
came to earth and was crucified.
He became the ultimate sin offering to
redeem all of humanity, brothers and sisters.
So let's
listen to a spiritual passage to help us
understand
what exactly was happening back then.
All right, here's the first one.
Would any brother or sister like to read?
Any brother or sister would like to read,
brothers and sisters?
It's
a spiritual passage that starts with, at
the time,
Jesus' work was to redeem all mankind.
Any volunteers?
Annette, would you like to read?
Mark?
Colby?
Edgar?
No worries, sister, no worries at all.
If not, no worries, I can read,
okay?
So the first one reads, At the time,
Jesus' work was to redeem all mankind.
The sins of all who believed in him were
forgiven.
As long as you believed in him,
he would redeem you.
If you believed in him, you were no longer
of sin.
You were relieved of your sins.
This is what it meant to be saved and to
be justified by faith.
Yet in those who believed,
there remained that which was rebellious
and opposed God,
and which still had to be slowly removed.
Salvation did not mean man had been
completely gained by Jesus, but that man
was no longer of sin, that he had been
forgiven his sins.
Provided you believed, you would never
more be of sin.
Amen.
And now, let's listen to the second
passage together, okay?
Let's understand the background of Jesus'
work, okay?
For in
the age of grace, the demons were cast out
from
man with the laying on of hands and prayer.
But the corrupt dispositions within man
still remained.
Man was healed of his sickness and
forgiven his sins.
But as for just
how man was to be purged of the corrupt
satanic dispositions
within him, this work had yet to be done.
Man was only saved and forgiven his sins
for his faith.
But the sinful nature of man was not
extirpated and still remained within him.
The sins of man were forgiven.
And this is because of the work.
Of God's crucifixion.
That man continued to live within his
corrupt satanic disposition of old.
This being so, man must be completely
saved from his corrupt satanic disposition.
So that his sinful nature may be
completely extirpated.
Never to develop again.
Thus, enabling the disposition of man.
To be transformed.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So let me ask you all a quick question,
okay?
After the Lord Jesus was crucified and
completed the work of redemption,
do we still need to offer animals as a sin
offering when we sin?
What do you think?
After the Lord Jesus was crucified and
completed the work of redemption,
do we still need to offer animals so that
our sins could be forgiven?
Exactly.
No, we don't.
Right?
No, we don't, my dear brothers and
sisters.
Absolutely not.
Okay?
The Lord Jesus was crucified as a sin
offering for all of humanity.
He redeemed us once and for all.
And because of this, we no longer need to
make animal offerings anymore.
As long as we confess and repent to the
Lord, our sins are forgiven.
We're no longer condemned or put to death
for violating the law.
Instead, we're qualified to come before
the Lord, pray to Him, and enjoy the
peace, the joy, and the abundant grace
that He gives us.
And that's the true meaning of being
saved.
Okay?
So
justification by faith, it means no more
animal
sacrifices, no longer condemned by the law.
Because the Lord Jesus, He was the
unblemished lamb.
He was the eternal sin offering to forgive
our sins.
So a lot of people love to say,
once saved, always saved.
That's not the case at all, brothers and
sisters.
Once saved, always saved is nothing but
man's interpretation.
Because the true meaning of being saved
during Jesus' time, it only means that
people's sins are forgiven.
It means we no longer need to offer sin
offerings.
It means we no longer are condemned by the
law.
That's all what it means.
We're justified by faith.
It doesn't mean, oh, the Lord Jesus died
on the cross for us.
We can now enter the kingdom of heaven.
No, that's not what it means.
It only means we're no longer condemned by
the law.
Meaning, whenever we commit a sin,
we pray, dear God, I'm so sorry for this.
Because you're saved by grace.
All right, brothers and sisters.
You're saved by grace.
So now, another question, right?
Exactly.
Amen, Sister Annette.
2,000 years ago, the Lord Jesus was
crucified to forgive our sins.
But did he completely remove our sinful
nature?
Did he completely remove our sinful
What do you think?
Exactly, right, Sister Annette?
What about other brothers and sisters?
Did he completely remove our sinful
nature?
No.
Right, Brother Kenneth?
Amen.
What about Edgar?
What do you think, Edgar?
What do you think, Rose and Colby and
Annie?
Amen, Jasmine.
What about Lisa?
What do you think, my dear Sister Lisa?
Amen.
Amen, Edgar.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
No.
Amen, bye.
Because even today, we're still sinning,
aren't we?
So from these words that we just read,
it's clear.
It's very clear.
The Lord Jesus only did the work of
redemption.
He did not do the work of cleansing and
transforming us.
He didn't transform us.
So us, by believing in the Lord,
yes, our sins are forgiven.
But our sinful nature has not yet been
resolved.
And the
sinful nature is the root cause of why we
constantly
sin even after our sins are forgiven.
So you see, being saved by faith,
it only means our sins are forgiven.
And we are no longer condemned or put to
death by the law.
But it doesn't mean we have stopped
sinning.
And it clearly, certainly does not mean
our sinful nature has been cleansed.
All right, brothers and sisters.
So once again, saved by faith.
Right?
It means our sins are forgiven only.
But sinful nature still remains.
So the work of redemption did not purify a
man.
Our sins are forgiven.
But the sinful nature remains.
And I'll give you an example so that you
can understand it.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
Imagine a thief.
Okay?
Imagine a thief who was so greedy,
who has a greedy nature.
And he loves to steal.
One day, he gets caught.
But because his father loves him so much,
he ended up bailing him out.
Now, does that guarantee that the thief
won't steal again?
His father bailed him out.
Does that mean the thief won't steal
again, brothers and sisters?
After his father bailed him out?
Amen, Sister Annette.
Anyone else?
Amen, Sister Jasmine.
Of course not.
Right?
He may be legally off the hook.
But remember, that greedy nature,
that urge to steal, it's still in there.
So as long as he has the right opportunity,
hey, he's going to steal again.
He's going to steal again, brothers and
sisters.
Because why?
He's got a greedy nature.
So stealing is the sinful behavior.
And the greed inside is the sinful nature.
All right, brothers and sisters?
So really, the sinful nature is the root
of sin.
And all sinful behavior stems from the
sinful nature.
Now,
if the sinful nature is not uprooted,
then
you'll never stop your sinful behavior.
It's almost like cutting grass.
Let me send you a picture.
Let me send you a lovely, lovely picture,
brothers and sisters.
Here we go.
Take a look.
Right?
Actually, that's not the picture I wanted
to send you guys.
There's another picture that I wanted to
send you guys, brothers and sisters.
There we go.
Those are two good pictures.
So you can have both of them in front of
you, okay?
You can have both of them in front of you,
brothers and sisters.
But take a look at the second picture,
right?
It's almost like grass.
How do you stop grass from growing back?
In
order for you to stop grass from growing back
you have to pull out the roots, right?
You have to pull out the roots in order to
stop the grass from growing.
Because if you're only mowing the lawn,
you are only cutting it near the base.
that grass is going to grow again and again and again and again ....
you seem new roots grow from the base and roots to
form new grass.
So the grass grows after being cut and it
is cut after growing, but why can't?
Why can they grow again after you cut it?
Because the roots are still attached to
it.
Well, brothers and sisters, this is the
problem of human sin.
The problem of our sinning, it's exactly
the same.
Because if our sins are only forgiven,
but the root of sin is not removed,
we're going to keep sinning.
And what is the root of sin inside of us,
brothers and sisters?
It's actually our satanic nature.
It's Satan's poison inside of us.
You get it?
It's like the grass, right?
One day your grass grows, you cut it by
the surface, it's going to grow again.
But if you cut it by the root,
it's never going to grow again.
Well, that's like us, brothers and
sisters.
What do we do?
We sin,
we ask for forgiveness, then we sin again,
then
we ask for forgiveness, then we sin again.
It's a repetition, right?
We're only asking for forgiveness.
Only the surface level of things.
You see, Satan's nature, brothers and
sisters, is made up of a lot of things.
And it goes back to the second picture
that I want to send you.
right there, OK?
Satan's nature is made up of corrupt
dispositions such as selfishness,
arrogance, crookedness, deceitfulness,
wickedness and greed and
self-righteousness and self-important...
you name it.
And I'll give you an example.
When our
interests or when our reputations are at stake
we find it hard to follow the Lord's words.
And we find it very hard to be an honest
person.
We worry that if we tell the truth,
people are going to look down on us.
so what do we do?
We lie instead.
You know what that is?
That's the deceitful, corrupt nature
inside of us.
You're a very deceitful person if you're
always lying.
A big lie and a small lie, that's still a
lie.
You're a deceitful.
Or what about arrogance?
Arrogance is another satanic disposition
because it drives us to brag, to look down
on others, and even to force others to
listen to us.
You see, when
the Lord Jesus forgave our sins, he spares
us from the
punishment that we deserve, which is death.
However, our sinful nature still remains,
okay, brothers and sisters?
So sin is bad behavior.
A sinful nature is what leads us to commit
sin.
So as long as our sinful nature is not
resolved, even if the Lord forgives us a
thousand
times, even if he forgives us a million
times,
we will not be able to stop sinning.
Why?
Because we have a sinful nature.
We still have Satan's poison.
We still
can't achieve holiness, and ultimately, we
still are not
qualified to enter the kingdom of heaven.
And yes, that's a hard fact that we have
to face because we have Satan's poison.
Brothers and sisters, are you following
along so far?
You following along?
We got poisons inside of us.
It all started in the Garden of Eden.
You know that, right?
It all started in the Garden of Eden,
brothers and sisters.
What happened?
God said,
out of the tree of the garden you can eat,
but from
this particular tree, you shall not eat.
And then what happened?
Satan came down and started to deceive
Adam and Eve, right?
And rather than listening to the word of
God, they listened to the word of Satan.
So that was Satan's...
That was Satan's objective is to really
get us to obey God.
It's for us to listen to him.
That's what he wanted, and he achieved it.
That's
why today we listen more to Satan's lies
rather than
listening to the truth that God expresses.
You see, this poison has been passed on
from generation to generation.
It's sad, but it's reality, brothers and
sisters.
You see, Satan did not corrupt the flesh.
Satan corrupted the mind.
he corrupted the mind
Satan always tells us what to do
It is all in the mind brothers and sisters, ok?
because it is your mind that tells your flesh what to do.
isn't that right?
That is why today, what we put in our mind
like, you know, the music that you listen to, you got to be careful what you listen to
You got to be careful with the movies that you watch
the music video that you watch
you got to be careful with what you see on TV
because it is all to corrupt your mind.
And then you start to think that it's
normal.
It's normal to behave like this.
It's normal to behave like that.
It's not.
This is Satan's
poison that he is instilling in each and
every single one of
us, so that we can reject the Word of God.
That's the whole problem, brothers and
sisters.
That's right, Sister Inek.
Right?
So brothers and sisters, you may be
thinking, right?
If that's true, if it's true that we don't
have a sinful nature, and it's true we
cannot
enter the Kingdom of Heaven right now, but
how
do we get rid of the sinful nature, right?
How do we get rid of the sinful nature?
And how do we enter the Kingdom of Heaven?
Because
brothers and sisters, do you think
we
can resolve the sinful nature on our own?
Do you think it's just by reading the
Bible, attending more gatherings,
and praying more, that's how we can
gradually remove our sinful nature?
You think it's that easy, brothers and
sisters?
You think it's that easy just attending
more gatherings, praying more,
and reading the Bible more?
What do you think?
Hmm.
No, it's not that easy.
Of course not.
It's not, brothers and sisters,
because you have to think about it.
For thousands of years, how many devout
Christians have read the Bible?
How many devout Christians have attended
more gatherings?
How many devout Christians have prayed
constantly?
But who has actually stopped sinning?
Who has actually broken free?
Or broken free from their corrupt
disposition?
Not a single one.
Even Paul said in the book of Romans,
For to will is present with me,
but how
to perform that which is good I find not."
You see, human
nature is full of Satanic disposition.
Satan's words have become our life.
In other
words, Satan's disposition have become so
deeply
rooted that they have become our very life.
And because of this, From their corrupt
disposition, No matter how hard we try to
restrain ourselves, it's completely
useless.
Brothers and sisters, look around.
Which believer has broken free from the
bondage of sin?
Nobody.
Are we
all still caught up in the cycle of sinning
and
confessing, and confessing and sinning?
We all struggle bitterly.
We even pray with tears in our eyes.
But yeah, we haven't broke free from sin.
So to break free from sin and to achieve
holiness, we don't just need the Lord
Jesus to be crucified and take on our
sins.
We need Him to personally
come back as the Son of Man, just
like how He prophesied
to remove the sinful nature inside of us.
This is deeper work now, brothers and
sisters.
That's why He comes back, because He knew
it wasn't done.
That's why He says,
I have many things to say to you, because
you cannot
bear what I'm doing and speaking right now.
That's why He comes.
He comes back to cleanse
and to transform us, so we can achieve
holiness and be
qualified to enter the kingdom of heaven.
Look what the Lord said.
He prophesied, I have yet many things to
say to you, but you cannot bear them now.
However, when He in the spirit of truth
has come, He will guide you into all truth.
Look at that.
He comes back to guide us into all truth.
You see that, brothers and sisters?
So when the Lord comes back, He has a new
work to do, which is the work of what?
Judgment.
And brothers and sisters, remember,
the work of judgment is something that was
already prophesied in the Bible in over
200 places.
For example, For the time has come that
judgment must begin at the house of God.
1 Peter 4.17 For the Father judges no man,
but has committed all judgment to the Son,
and has given him authority to execute
judgment also.
Why?
Because He is the Son of Man.
John 5.22-27 And if any man hears My words
and believes not, I judge him not.
For I came not to judge the world,
but to save the world.
He that rejects Me and accepts not My
words, has one that judges him
The word that I have spoken, the same
shall judge him in the last day.
John 12.47-48 Now these verses,
you could see that in the last days,
the Lord returns as the Son of Man to do
the work of judgment.
And it is this work of judgment that helps
us completely cast off sin, break free
from Satan's influence, and gain complete
salvation.
Brothers and sisters, it's only by
accepting God's work of judgment in the
last days, can our corruptions be
cleansed.
And really, judgment is our only path into
the Kingdom of Heaven.
Redemption wasn't.
It's the judgment, brothers and sisters.
So you see, 2000 years ago, it was the
work of redemption.
It was to forgive our sins.
But brothers and sisters, in the last
days, it is the work of judgment.
And what is the work of judgment?
It is to cast off our sinful nature and to
cleanse us.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Let's do some reading, okay?
Let's do some spiritual readings here
together.
I've got two passages that we're going to
read.
All right.
Give me one moment.
So the first
one reads, Before man was redeemed, many
of Satan's poisons
had already been planted within him.
And after
thousands of years of being corrupted by
Satan, he
has within him a nature that resists God.
Therefore, when man was redeemed, it
was nothing more than a case of redemption.
That is, man was bought back at a high
price.
But the poisonous nature within him was
not eliminated.
Man that is so filthy must undergo a
change before becoming worthy to serve God.
By means of this work of judgment and
chastisement, man will fully come to know
the filthy and
corrupt essence within his own self, and
he will be able
to change completely and become purified.
Only in this way can man be worthy to
return before the throne of God.
Amen.
And one more passage, okay?
There we go.
I'll wait till everybody gets it.
Let's listen carefully.
Though Jesus did
much work among man, he only completed the
redemption of
all mankind and became man's sin offering.
He did not rid man of all his corrupt
disposition.
Fully saving man from the influence of
Satan not only required Jesus to become
the sin offering and bear the sins of man,
but it also required God to do even
greater work to rid man completely of his
satanically corrupted disposition.
And so, now that man has been forgiven of
his sins, God has returned to the flesh
to lead man into the new age and begun the
work of chastisement and judgment.
This work has brought man into a higher
realm.
All
those who submit under his dominion shall
enjoy higher
truth, and receive greater blessings.
They shall truly live in the light,
and they shall gain the truth,
the way, and the life.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Great passages, no?
Because the Lord Jesus did the work of
redemption.
Isn't that right?
And through faith in him that we all have,
our sins are forgiven.
But our sinful nature remains,
causing us to sin constantly.
So
God has to do the stage of judgment work
beginning
at the house of God in the last days.
And this is to let people completely cast
off sin and their corrupt disposition,
to truly follow God's will and enter into
the kingdom of heaven.
You see, the work of judgment in the last
days is not just about condemning humanity.
Instead, brothers and sisters,
it's a cleansing work.
It's about cleansing and to save us, those
who truly can welcome the Lord's return.
So the
fact that judgment begins at the house of
God is actually
God's love and his salvation for us.
You see, the work of judgment is our only
path to completely break free from the
bondage of sin and our only hope of
entering the kingdom of heaven.
Because
once we're cleansed and no longer bound by
sin, we're
truly free and able to enter God's kingdom.
Now, isn't that a much higher realm?
So God's work of judgment
in the last days is actually the most
crucial and important
stage in his work of saving humanity.
It will determine whether we can enter the
kingdom of heaven or not.
So, if someone misses this critical stage
and rejects the work of judgment in the
last days, they will not be cleansed by
God.
And in the end, all their efforts in
following God will eventually all be in vain.
Just like the Pharisees.
They followed Jehovah, but they couldn't
accept the Lord Jesus.
So all their efforts was all in vain,
brothers and sisters.
Right?
So we don't want to put our efforts in
vain.
Because if that was the case, we won't be
qualified to enter the kingdom of heaven.
And our faith will be a complete failure.
And that will be a long life regret.
Alright?
So let's do a little bit of a comparison
here.
Let's do a comparison.
The work of redemption was to forgive our
sins.
It's like cutting off the branch of a
tree.
You can cut off the branch of a tree as
many times as you want.
The tree is still going to grow.
Right?
Because you're only cutting the surface of
it.
You're only trimming the branches.
But the work of judgment is something a
little bit deeper.
Right?
The work of judgment is to purify our
sinful nature, brothers and sisters.
It's really removing the tree.
The tree roots.
Because
if you remove the entire root of the tree,
you
know that tree will never grow back again.
Amen.
So let's answer some questions here.
Okay?
Let's answer some questions, brothers and
sisters.
What do you think?
Why does the Lord Jesus come back to do
the work of judgment in the last days?
Would you say A, He's coming back to
forgive our sins again?
Would you say B, to cast off our sinful
nature so we can be cleansed?
Or would you say C, I don't need judgment.
Anyone who believes in the Lord can enter
the kingdom of heaven.
What do you think, my dear brothers and
sisters?
What is the correct answer?
Amen, Jasmine.
Amen, Edgar.
What about others?
Amen, Sister May.
Amen, Neves.
Amen, amen.
Amen, Sister Rose.
Amen, Sister Annette.
That's right.
Anyone else, brothers and sisters?
What do you think, Sister Patricia?
Liza?
What do you think?
Kim?
Cicely?
Annie?
Monica?
Lindsay?
Bobby?
Samuel?
What do you think?
Steve?
Lisa?
Akunz?
Alex?
And Butt?
Abraham?
What do you think?
Jeff?
Kenneth?
What do you think?
Obina?
And Marvin?
Elaine?
What do you think?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Drum roll, please.
So, Brother Kenneth, no.
God does not repeat his work, my dear
Brother Kenneth.
He's not going to come back to forgive
your sins again.
Think about the Lord Jesus, brother.
Did the Lord Jesus come back to repeat
what Jehovah God already did?
Did Jesus repeat the laws and
commandments?
No.
He redeemed us from the laws and
commandments.
Jesus came back to do the work.
He came to do the work of redemption.
Now, when
the Lord comes back again, brother,
you really think
God is going to repeat that work again?
You think he's going to redeem us again?
That's not God.
God doesn't repeat his work, Brother
Kenneth.
Just like everybody else said,
it is B.
The correct answer is B.
Okay?
B is the correct answer, brothers and
sisters.
He comes back to cast off our sinful
nature so we can be cleansed.
It's about the work of judgment now.
Judgment is far different than the
redemption.
So, yes, Sister Annie, we need the
judgment.
Anyone who believes needs the judgment in
order to enter God's kingdom.
Okay?
Now, maybe let me ask another question to
see if brothers and sisters are clear.
Take a look at this one, Sister Annie and
Brother Kenneth.
This
one says, If we only accept the Lord Jesus'
redemption,
can we enter the kingdom of heaven?
If you only accept the redemption?
A. No
The Lord Jesus' work only redeemed us from
sin.
But it didn't cast off our sinful nature.
We need God to return and to do the work
of judgment to cleanse us.
Only then do we have a chance to enter the
kingdom of heaven.
Or B. Our sins are forgiven by believing in the
Lord Jesus.
So we can enter the kingdom of heaven when
he returns.
We don't need to accept God's judgment
work.
There you go, Brother Kenneth.
Amen, my dear brother.
Amen, Sister Rose.
Amen.
What about others, brothers and sisters?
What do you think, Annie?
You can try again.
What do you think, Sister Annette?
Amen, Sister Neves.
Amen, amen.
What about Lisa?
Jasmine?
Sister May?
What do you think?
Is it A. No
We are only redeemed, but we still have a
sinful nature.
Or B. Our sins are forgiven. Of course we can enter.
Hmm.
Very close, Sister Annette.
Very close.
What about you, Brother Edgar?
That's right, my dear brother.
A is the correct answer, brothers and
sisters.
All right?
Remember, the Lord Jesus only redeemed us
from sin.
He did his ministry for three and a half
years.
Right?
We are only redeemed, brothers and
sisters.
But he did not cast off our sinful nature.
Remember, we still sin.
The Lord Jesus forgave mankind 2,000 years
ago.
Look yourself in the mirror.
We still sin.
We all do.
So we do need God to return.
We do need God to do greater work,
which is the cleansing.
Which is the cleansing in order for us to
enter the kingdom of heaven.
All right?
Amen.
Brothers and sisters, are you clear so
far?
Clear so far?
We need more work.
That I think we can all agree,
right?
We need more work.
We definitely do.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
So let's talk about how exactly does God
do the work of judgment to cleanse us.
Would you guys like to know?
Brothers and sisters, would you like to
know how he does it?
Would
you like to know how God cleanses us
and
how he carries out the work of judgment?
Let's have a look, right?
It's all about seeking the truth together.
Amen, Kenneth.
Yeah.
Many brothers and sisters said yes.
Okay.
So let's find out.
Okay?
It's actually very practical.
We're going to read some verses and you
will see.
You will see, brothers and sisters.
First and foremost, once again,
what did the Lord say?
He said, I have yet many things to say to
you.
But you cannot bear them now.
However, when he, the spirit of truth,
has come, he will guide you into all truth.
And also, and you shall know the truth,
the truth shall set you free.
Sanctify them through your truth,
your word is truth.
For the word of God is quick and powerful,
sharp than any two-edged sword,
piercing even to the dividing asunder of
soul and spirit.
And of joints and marrow.
And it is a dissenter of the thoughts and
the intents of the heart.
Did anyone catch it?
From these
verses, do you know what God uses in the
last days
to do the work of judgment to cleanse us?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
What does he use?
Did you catch it?
Did anyone catch it?
What does he use?
What does he use to do the work of
judgment and to cleanse us?
There's a word right there that stands out
the most.
Not a two-edged sword, but there's
exactly, Brother Edgar.
Amen. Anyone else?
It's the truth, brothers and sisters.
It's the word of God.
It's the word.
Christ does the work of judgment with the
truth.
All of them are literally talking about
the truth.
Look, I have yet many things to say to
you.
He will guide you into all truth.
You shall know the truth.
Sanctify them through the truth.
For the word of God is quick and powerful.
It's all talking about the word of God,
brothers and sisters.
Right?
That's why, remember, what did the Lord
say?
In order for us to recognize him,
we have to hear his voice.
Brothers and sisters, look, they go hand
in hand.
When he becomes flesh, you have to
recognize him by his words.
Why?
Because he comes back to carry out the
work of judgment.
What is the work of judgment?
It is the use of the truth to cleanse us.
You
see, God expresses the truth in the last days
doing the work of judgment with his words.
And yes, the word of God is like a
sharp...
two-edged sword that can pierce right
through our hearts and our spirits.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
Now, let's go deeper, okay?
And
I want you guys to pay close attention to this part
because we're going to go deeper.
Brothers
and sisters, where is the truth God
God expresses
for his judgment in the last days?
Is it the words which...
we have already been recorded in the
Bible?
Or does God speak new words in the last
days?
But to answer that, let's look at a
prophecy first, okay?
Before you answer that, brothers and
sisters, before you answer that,
is
it going to be the same words in the Bible
or is it going to be the words outside?
First, look at this prophecy.
The Lord said, I have yet many things to
say to you.
You cannot bear... them now.
However, when he, the spirit of truth,
has come, he will guide you into all truth.
So, many things means all the truth.
You see, there are words the Lord has
never spoken before.
No one has ever heard it before.
Things that are not recorded in the Bible,
God will speak in the last days.
So, you have to ask yourselves,
could these words have been recorded in the Bible
ahead of time?
Now, you can answer the question.
Where can we find the words that the Lord
uses for his work of judgment in the last days
to cleanse us?
A. The words in the Bible that we've been
reading.
Or B. New
words outside of the Bible that God will express
when he returns in the last days.
Or C. I didn't catch it.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Let's see who's actually thinking outside
of the box.
Amen, Brother Kenneth.
Amen, Sister Rose.
Amen, Sister Annette.
Amen, Brother Edgar.
Amen.
Amen, Sister Jasmine.
Didn't even see your answer.
Amen, Sister Annie.
Amen.
Brothers and Sisters.
If I said Amen to your name.
Amen, Nieves.
What about Ba?
What do you think, Ba?
I'll wait for your answer because I see
you typing.
Ah, okay.
Close enough.
Brothers and Sisters.
The correct answer is B.
So, Sister Kim.
Sister Mae.
Brother Ba.
The correct answer is B.
Yes.
There
will be new words outside of the Bible that
God will
express when He returns in the last days.
Did you not catch the clue?
The Lord said, I have many things to say
to you.
Obviously, if He has many things to say to
us, it's because He hasn't spoken yet.
So, if He hasn't spoken yet, how can it be
in the Bible in advance?
Hello?
Right?
So, you
may be thinking, Sister Thelma, do you even
have proof
that there are new words in the last days?
Brothers and Sisters, of course I do.
Matter of fact, the Bible talks about a
sealed book many times.
This points out to God coming back to
speak new words in the last days.
Have a look.
Let's read it together.
That's no problem.
Look, the first one is in the book of
Revelation.
What is the book of Revelation?
There are prophecies of the end time that
the Lord still needs to fulfill.
So, the first one reads, And I saw in the
right hand of him that sat on the throne a
book written within and on the backside
sealed with seven seals.
And I saw a strong
angel proclaiming with a loud voice,
who is worthy to open the
book and to lose the seven seals thereof?
And no man in heaven nor in earth neither
under the earth was able to open the book
neither to look thereon.
And I wept much because no man was found
worthy to open and to read the book
neither to look thereon.
And one of the elders said to me,
Weep not!
Behold, the Lion of the tribe of Judah,
the Root of David, has prevailed to open
the book and to lose the seven seals
thereof.
Revelation 5 1 5 But you, O Daniel,
shut up the words and seal the book,
even to the time of the end.
Many shall run to and fro, and knowledge
shall be increased.
Daniel
12 4 Go your way, Daniel, for the words
are closed
up and sealed till the time of the end.
Many shall be purified and made white and
tried.
But the wicked shall do wickedly,
and none of the wicked shall understand,
but the wise shall understand.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
I hope you were able to catch a lot in
these prophecies, because I did.
These verses clearly mention there is
going to be a new book in the last days.
But what are the features?
What are the key features of this sealed
book?
Well, look at the difference first of all,
brothers and sisters.
The Bible, it's open to all.
The sealed book is sealed, meaning it's
closed.
The Bible, everyone can read it.
Matter of fact, we're reading it right
now.
But the sealed book, only the Lord Jesus
can open it.
The Bible, they're God's words from the
past.
The sealed book, it is to be opened in the
last days.
You see these key features, brothers and
sisters?
The sealed book, it was prophesied that it
is closed.
It's sealed at the moment, right?
Because
2,000 years ago, John, by the way,
the
book of Revelation was written by John.
And John said, no man in heaven nor in
earth, neither under the earth,
was able to open the book, neither to look
there on.
Now he's talking about people 2,000 years
ago, right?
Because the book of Revelation was written
2,000 years ago.
So at that particular time, no man could
have opened it.
It was closed.
And he started to cry because John
actually wanted to open the book.
But one of the elders told him,
don't cry.
Only the Lord Jesus can open it,
right?
It's mentioned, the Lion of the tribe of
Judah, the Root of David.
That means only the returned Lord Jesus
can personally open.
Only
the return of the Lord Jesus, because
2,000
years ago, Jesus never opened up a book.
No, he didn't.
So if Jesus never
opened up the book 2,000 years ago, then
you should
ask yourself, when can this book be opened?
Brothers and sisters, look what it says.
God
said, but you, O Daniel, shut up the words
and
seal the book, even to the time of the end.
This book can only be opened in the last
days, brothers and sisters.
In the last days.
So this seal book definitely is not the
Bible that we read every day.
It's not even the book of Revelation.
The Bible has been around for thousands of
years.
We can open it, we can read it every
single day.
But the seal book, on the other hand,
is new.
It's a new book that the Lord will bring
when he comes back.
You see, and what's the purpose of the
seal book?
Does anyone know?
What's the purpose of the seal book,
brothers and sisters?
It has a lot to do with God's work of
judgment.
What's the purpose of the seal book,
brothers and sisters?
Pay close attention.
It has to do with our topic today.
What's our topic today?
The judgment.
What is judgment for?
Why does God come back to do the work of
judgment?
If you can know why
God comes back to do the work of judgment,
Then you will
know what is the purpose of the seal book.
That's right, Sister Jasmine.
You hit the nail right on the head.
That's right, Neves.
You also hit the nail right on the head.
Brothers and sisters, the purpose of the
seal book, look, it is to purify us.
It is to cleanse us, brothers and sisters.
Look what God told Daniel.
many shall be purified and made
white and tried.
Look, the purpose of the seal book,
it is to purify us.
What is the work of judgment?
The work of judgment is the use of the
truth to purify us, to cleanse us.
So God already knew that he would be
speaking more words in the end time.
In order to purify us.
Look at that, brothers and sisters.
The words in the seal book is used to
cleanse us.
So now I think you can all agree to this
question.
Is the seal book the Bible or is it an
entirely new book?
I think everyone can answer this question
correctly now, right?
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Is the seal book?
The Bible or entirely a new book that God
will bring when he comes back?
That's right, Brother Edgar.
Amen, Annette.
Amen, Jasmine.
Amen, Annie and Kim and Kenneth.
What do you know?
Amen.
Amen, Rosie.
Amen, Sister Neves.
What about you, Brother Colby?
What about you?
That's right, brothers and sisters.
Entirely a new book.
A new book, brothers and sisters.
The correct answer is definitely B.
It's new.
It has to be new.
So to summarize it, my dear brothers and
sisters, right?
I want to summarize it.
You see, the Bible, the Bible only contains
the words that God has spoken in the past.
The seal book are words that will be open
when the Lord comes back.
So it's obviously not the Bible,
right?
It's obviously not the Bible, brothers and
sisters.
The words he expresses when he returns are
completely new, right?
So he came in the flesh for the first
time.
It was for the redemption to forgive us.
But coming in the flesh a second time is
for the judgment in order to remove our sin.
And God will express words that we
obviously have never heard before.
Words that he has never spoken before.
So naturally, they aren't recorded in the
Bible.
They're words that no one has ever heard
before.
So in the last days, the Lord returns to
express new words and to open up the seal book
for the work of judgment to begin and
to cleanse us.
So kind of do a comparison, okay,
brothers and sisters?
Because you see, God actually saves
mankind step by step.
God saves mankind step by step.
Look at the second picture that I'm about
to send you, right?
Because when God issued the laws and
commandments so we know what sin is,
you can actually read that in the Old
Testament.
And then, when
God became flesh for the very first time
to carry
out the work of redemption, which was what?
A whole new generation already.
It was to forgive our sins.
And what did they have?
They had the New Testament.
But what about us, brothers and sisters?
Our generation, right?
Because he comes back for the judgment in
order to purify our sins.
What are we going to have?
We're going to have the sealed book.
You see that, brothers and sisters?
This was something that was planned by God
a long time ago.
You see, brothers and sisters, as God's
work progresses, his words also progress.
So piggybacking off of last night.
In the last days, does the Lord come as a
spiritual body to express the truth?
Or does he become flesh a second time to
express the truth?
Is it A, he becomes flesh as an ordinary,
normal son of man to express the truth?
Or B, he does it as a spiritual body?
Or C, you're still not sure, brothers and
sisters?
I think when we put all the clues
together, I think brothers and sisters,
we're finally understanding, right?
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
That's right, Kenneth.
That's right, Jasmine.
That's right, Edgar and Annette.
And amen, brothers and sisters.
Good sharing, everybody.
That's right, A is the correct answer.
Yes, he becomes flesh in order to carry
out this work of judgment, okay?
So let's do some reading here tonight,
brothers and sisters.
I got a long spiritual passage that we're
going to listen together.
So you can understand, first of all, that
the work of judgment, that's God's work.
But what is he going to judge us on,
okay?
Let's listen to these passages together,
Here we go.
The work of judgment is God's own work.
So it must naturally be carried out by God Himself
It cannot be done by man in his stead.
Because judgment is the use of the truth
to conquer humankind, there is no question
that God would still appear in the incarnate
image to perform this work among man.
That
is to say, Christ of the last days shall
use
the truth to teach people across the world.
And make all truths known to them.
This is God's work of judgment.
Christ of the last days uses a variety of
truths to teach man.
To expose the substance of man.
And to dissect the words and deeds of man.
These words comprise various truths.
Such as man's duty.
How man should obey God.
How man should be loyal to God.
How man ought to live out normal humanity.
As well as the wisdom and the disposition
of God.
And so on.
These words are all directed at the
substance of man and his corrupt disposition.
In particular,
the words that expose how man spurns God
are spoken in regard
to how man is an embodiment of Satan.
And an enemy force against God.
In undertaking
his work of judgment, God does not
simply make
clear the nature of man with a few words.
He exposes, deals with, and prunes over
the long term.
All these
different methods of exposure, dealing, and
pruning
cannot be substituted with ordinary words.
But with the truth of which man is utterly
bereft.
Only methods such as these can be called
judgment.
Only
through judgment of this kind can man be
subdued
and thoroughly convinced about God.
And moreover, gain true knowledge of God.
What
the work of judgment brings about is
man's
understanding of the true face of God.
And the truth about his own
rebelliousness.
The work of judgment allows man to gain
much understanding of the will of God.
Of the purpose of God's work.
And of the mysteries that are
incomprehensible to him.
It
also allows man to recognize and know his
corrupt
essence and the roots of his corruption.
As well as to discover the ugliness of
man.
These effects are all brought about by the
work of judgment.
For the essence of this work is actually
the work of opening up the truth,
the way, and the life of God to all those
who have faith in him.
This work is the work of judgment done by
God.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
You see, brothers and sisters,
judgment isn't about digging up the past.
God is not going to do that.
It's not about condemning us all over
again for the sins that we committed.
Remember, we're forgiven already.
So, judgment is about judging the truth of
how Satan has corrupted us.
It judges
our satanic nature, our satanic essence,
and
the satanic dispositions inside of us.
It judges absolutely everything in us that
is incompatible with God.
And at the end of the day, judgment is
just here to cleanse us.
The whole point is to achieve the result
of cleansing.
To use judgment
to get rid of all those unclean things
like our
satanic nature and our satanic disposition.
So, after reading these passages,
brothers and sisters, it's totally clear.
God becoming flesh in the last days to do
the work of judgment is him becoming flesh
a second time as the Son of Man to express
the truth and do this work.
Every single word of God carries authority.
And His words are the truth.
And only God can scrutinize our innermost
hearts.
Isn't that right?
So, what does he do?
He uses His words to reveal our different
satanic dispositions.
He
uses to reveal the wrong thoughts and the
views
that Satan has fed us year after year.
So God's words will expose how we live out
our corrupt dispositions like what?
Arrogance, deceit and wickedness.
And they hit the nail right on the head,
because it'll expose our mixed motives for
following
God, the thoughts deeply hidden in our
hearts,
and the real motives behind what we do.
So when we see our filthy, corrupt,
and ugly faces completely revealed by God,
don't you think you're going to feel
ashamed?
Because I know I will, right?
And that's when we want to find a hole to
hide in, right?
Because we'll realize
that, wow, we actually don't deserve
to live before
God, because we're actually so filthy.
And it's right then that we truly thirst
to understand and gain the truth.
So we start to reflect on ourselves
through the Word of God.
We look for the root of our sins.
We get to know our corrupt dispositions.
And at the same time, we find the path in
the Word of God to resolve our problems.
And during
this time, God places us in different
environments,
including trials and refinement.
And we have to battle our corrupt
dispositions over and over again.
And when we rebel against the flesh and
practice the truth, that's the only way
our poisons can slowly fall off and are
cast off.
And once we understand the truth,
we can actually live by the Word of God.
That's right, brothers and sisters.
Our life dispositions will change.
Then we actually have hope.
We have hope of ultimately entering the
kingdom of heaven.
Hope of being cleansed by the Word of God.
We can actually become people who
basically submit to God and stop opposing God
and be brought into the kingdom of
heaven.
And this process is the process of being
cleansed by the Word of God.
Brothers
and sisters, when I say you got to be a lover of the truth.
I'm not playing around.
You got to be a lover of the truth,
brothers and sisters.
Every day,
you got to be in the Word of God, because
God speaks new
words to carry out the work of judgment.
So you could see the work of judgment is
nothing supernatural.
It doesn't happen in an instant.
It doesn't happen in a day or two like
people imagine.
No, no, no, brothers and sisters.
The total opposite.
In the last days, God personally becomes
flesh on earth, expresses a lot of words
in order to carry out his work of
judgment.
He uses his words to expose people's
corruption.
He uses his words to point out the path of
casting off our corrupt disposition.
People can truly reflect on and know
themselves based on the Word of God,
so that they can cast off anything inside
of them that is not of God.
So the process
of the Son of Man expressing the truth is
the process of
God doing the work of judgment to save us.
So God expresses the truth and does the
work of judgment because we are the ones
that are We are the ones that are
corrupted by Satan.
We are the ones that have a nature that
opposes God.
Our corrupt disposition is the root of our
opposition to God.
It is one of the hardest things to
resolve.
Come on.
We've tried it.
We can't do it on our own.
God has to come back to do it.
Right?
It has to be resolved through judgment and
chastisement.
So God's words, brothers and sisters, it's
alongside with the trials and refinement.
We absolutely have to accept God's work so
we can submit to him, worship him,
and be saved by him.
And I'll give you another example.
Hopefully, this example will make sense.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
Think about a sick person going to see a
doctor.
You see, when
a patient arrives at the hospital,
you know that the doctor cannot
just immediately jump you into surgery.
The doctor can't even immediately give you
out pills.
Instead, the doctor has to figure out what
exactly is wrong with you, right?
So that he knows how to treat you.
Well, God's work of judgment is exactly
like that.
You see, God expresses the truth to first,
let you know
which of our behavior are sinful and which are opposing God.
You know, , things like lying, getting
jealous of one another, being arrogant,
being self-righteous.
Hey, the list goes on.
We've got it.
You name it, we've got it.
And then he tells us how to resolve these
problems.
He points out a way for us to live a true
human likeness.
And by reading by
the word of God, little by little,
can we find the path
to cast off our sin and be cleansed by God.
And this
is the true path process of God doing the
work of
judgment, like a doctor treating a patient.
It takes time.
Takes time to heal, doesn't it?
Well, it's going to take time for us to
finally be perfected by God.
Brothers and sisters, are you
understanding?
Are you understanding that the path to the
kingdom of heaven is very real,
very practical?
It's not just about, oh, my sins are
forgiven by the blood of the lamb.
I can be taken in the air and enter the
kingdom of heaven.
No.
That's wishful thinking.
That's man's wishful thinking.
Never was that in the word of God.
It's totally unrealistic.
Because if we want
to be taken into the kingdom of heaven,
the most crucial
thing is to accept the work of judgment.
It's to accept the new words in the seal
book.
Put it into practice.
That's the only way our corruptions can be
cleansed.
That's the only way we can be people who
actually do the will of the Father.
And that's the only way we can inherit
all that God has, all the blessings, right?
Everything that he has to give us.
Okay, brothers and sisters.
So in summary, in order to enter the
kingdom of heaven, what do we need to do?
We need to be holy.
Right?
And in order for us to be holy,
what do we need to do?
We need to cast off our sinful nature and
be cleansed.
And how do we cast off our sinful nature
and be cleansed?
You've got to accept the work of judgment.
And by accepting the work of judgment,
What are you going to do?
Accept the new words in the sealed book
and welcome the Lord's return.
Amen brothers and sisters.
Is everyone clear so far?
Brothers and sisters, are we clear so far?
What do you think?
Amen, amen brothers and sisters.
Amen.
We're almost done by the way.
Okay we're almost done.
We're coming to the last part already. Okay?
Amen brothers and sisters.
Because we just took an hour and a half to
talk about the judgment for the believers. Right?
So, the work of judgment, brothers and
sisters, it actually has two aspects.
Cleansing God's chosen people and actually
condemning the non-believers who reject it.
Because both of them happen at the same
time.
So those who ask, right brothers and
sisters, those who can accept the judgment work.
work, God will use the truth to cleanse
and to purify them.
But what about those who do not accept?
What about those who do not accept?
Ain't that right?
So, in other words, right, for
non-believers or those who only believe in
the Lord Jesus but reject His second
incarnation, people who only cling to the
Bible
but reject the new words God expresses
in
the last days, how does God judge them?
How does He do it?
Well... Well, brothers and
sisters, let me read to you two passages.
I think
after these two passages, you're going to
know
what happens to those who reject the truth.
Alright?
Here we go.
One aspect
of God's work is to conquer all mankind
and
gain the chosen people through His words.
Another is to conquer all sons of
rebellion by ways of various disasters.
This is one part of the large scale work.
Only in this way can the kingdom on earth
that God wants be fully achieved.
And this is the part of His work that is
pure gold.
All manner of disasters will befall one
after another.
All nations and places will experience
calamities.
Plague, famine, flood, drought,
and earthquakes are everywhere.
These disasters are not just happening in
one or two places.
Nor will they happen over within a day or
two.
Rather, instead, they will expand over a
greater and greater area.
And become more and more severe.
During this time, all manner of insect
plagues will arise one after another.
And the phenomenon of cannibalism will
occur everywhere.
This is my judgment upon the myriad
countries and people.
So you can see, right brothers and
sisters?
Yesterday we spoke that there are two ways
of the Lord's return.
One, as the Son of Man.
And two, when He finally reveals the spiritual body
for all mankind to see.
Well, guess what?
Judgment falls into two types,
brothers and sisters.
Judgment falls into two types.
There is judgment for the believers.
Because remember, judgment begins at the
house of God.
Those are God's chosen people.
They will be judged by the new words of
God.
But remember, us being judged by the new
words of God.
That is a purification and salvation.
Compared to the non-believers and those
false believers.
Those who oppose God.
They are going to receive judgment by
disasters.
Which will be a punishment.
So, if you are passively waiting to see
God return on a white cloud.
Brothers and sisters, you are basically
just waiting for your day of death.
Really.
That is all you are waiting for.
You see, God does His work in steps.
In stages, which we will talk about
tomorrow.
It is not done in one go.
The first stage is God becoming flesh
again.
To do the work of judgment beginning at
the house of God.
To express the truth.
To cleanse and to perfect a group of
overcomers.
We call that a salvation.
The second stage is when the Lord appears
on a white cloud.
Well, the work of judgment is finished.
It is to reward the good and punish the
wicked.
Right? That is why judgment is a double-edged
sword.
Do you know what a double-edged sword is?
Both sides are piercing.
Right? A double-edged sword.
It is a sword that has both sides.
So, think about it brothers and sisters.
One side is going to pierce you.
But it is going to cleanse you.
And perfect you.
The other side is going to pierce you.
But it is going to destroy you.
So God does work by his words is mainly to
cleanse those who can accept, right?
And
the judgment of words, he achieves the result
of cleansing and saving a group of people.
But at the same time, brothers and
sisters, those who clearly know the Bible
has so many prophecies about God doing the
final work of judgment in the last days,
but you want to reject it?
Well, what do you think is going to
happen?
You'll be the target of God's condemnation
and elimination.
You'll all be left for the disasters to be
destroyed.
You see, God's work of judgment is about
cleansing and saving people.
It's also the work of sorting people
according to their kind.
It's not just about condemning and
destroying.
No.
The work of judgment is about rewarding
the good and punishing the wicked.
It happens at the same time, brothers and
sisters.
And
during the time God is working in the flesh again.
yes, he will express the truth.
Yes, he will save his chosen people.
Those who truly believe in God,
those who love the truth,
God will make into first fruits, meaning they will be
the overcomers.
They'll completely break free from their
poisons.
They'll be cleansed.
They'll achieve salvation.
And they're the ones that will be qualified
to enter the kingdom of heaven directly.
But when God becomes flesh to express the
truth, if you don't want to accept it,
well, it's too late.
If
you just wait for him to come on a white
cloud,
that's when the work of judgment is over.
Okay?
That's why the Bible says many shall wail
because of him.
You're going to wail, brothers and
sisters.
Because why?
It's a time of punishing the wicked.
And by then, you don't want to be filled
with gut-wrenching regret, do you?
No, you don't.
Because at the end of the day,
God is not going to repeat his work at all.
All that awaits is nothing but disaster and punishment
So, that's why we say, judgment is directly
tied to everyone's final destination.
It's
a critical issue that decides whether a
believer
can get into the kingdom of heaven or not.
It's up to you.
Whether you want to accept or not.
Remember, God gives us free will.
If you don't want to accept, okay.
Right?
Okay, that's fine, brothers and sisters.
If you want to treat it based on your own
notions and imaginings, okay,
then you will forever lose the chance to be cleansed by God.
An eternal regret, an eternal pain.
And this is exactly how God will end the age.
He saves a group of people who love the
truth and accepts the truth, but at the
same time, he condemns and destroys those
who oppose the truth.
After all, this is God's work of judgment.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
So now, my dear brothers and sisters,
now that we're on this topic,
I want to ask you guys a final question,
okay?
And then we'll talk about this question.
Here we go.
Take a look, brothers and sisters.
Take a look, right?
If a pastor ever tells you, and I'm being
honest, brothers and sisters, okay?
I'm being honest.
If a pastor ever tells you that,
no, you are saved by faith.
If the pastor says, the Lord Jesus' blood
has washed away your sins, as long as you
read the Bible often and pray every day,
you can enter the kingdom.
If a pastor
says, we believers, we don't need the
Lord to
do the work of judgment in the last days.
We don't need the work of cleansing,
right?
We don't need the work of cleansing and
saving us.
Just continue to read the Bible.
That's enough.
We don't need God to express new words.
There's no such a thing as the sealed
book.
Brothers and sisters, are you going to
agree with the pastor that tells you this?
Be honest, okay?
Because, hey, they may will.
Are you going to agree with the pastor
that says that?
What do you think, Edgar and Annette?
Yeah, me too.
Missed me with that, right?
Are you going to agree, Sister Annette?
Sister Rose?
Colby?
Yeah, me either.
I'm definitely not going to agree.
Sorry, Alex.
You're on your own for this one,
buddy.
Absolutely not.
I'm not agreeing with that.
At the end of the day, who gives me
salvation?
Who gives us salvation?
It is God, not the pastors.
It is God that gives salvation.
You see, that's the problem.
Today, many
people in the religious world, they say
there's no
way that God will do the work of judgment.
Because why?
They're
just waiting for the Lord to come on a
white cloud
so they can enter the kingdom of heaven.
These people are waiting for blessings.
That's all.
And that's not the right view.
The Lord
Jesus never said that in order to enter the
kingdom
of heaven, you need to be saved by faith.
No, he didn't.
You see, God does the work of judgment in
the last days, and it's totally backed up
by biblical prophecies.
One being that judgment begins at the
house of God.
So some pastors clearly know that the
Bible prophesies about the work of judgment
but yet they deny it and they
reject it.
Do you really believe in the Bible,
brothers and sisters?
Do you believe in the word of God?
Yeah, we should, right?
Because in our faith, you can't just
blindly trust what pastors say.
We have to base everything in the Lord
Jesus's words.
If what
people tell us does, not match with what
Jesus
said, then why would you listen to them?
For those who do not
listen to the word of God, okay, okay, you
can be blinded by
the pastors like they were 2000 years ago.
If you're, if
you are not in the word of God every day,
then it's easy for
the word of your pastors to deceive you.
Okay.
It means you lack discernment,
right?
It means
you lack discernment because you don't have
the word of God rooted in your heart.
That
means when the Lord does come back to
do
the work of judgment, you won't accept it.
So what happens?
All awaits for them is endless disasters.
Remember, you ought to obey God rather
than men.
So we could see God's work of judgment is
actually crucial.
It is the work of salvation.
So by accepting the judgment, we can be
made into an overcomer.
Accepting the judgment, we get to know our
own corruption.
We come to know God's righteous and holy
disposition.
We gradually come to understand the truth
and gain the truth.
And when we do, we are gradually cleansed.
And this is the only path for people to be
saved.
Now, if you reject, you'll never break
free from the bondage of sin.
You'll never break free from Satan,
brothers and sisters.
If you do
not accept God's work of judgment, you'll
never,
ever, ever know how Satan corrupts you.
You'll just continue to be corrupted by
Satan.
You'll continue to rebel against God,
oppose God, deny God, betray God.
And in the end, just like the days of Noah, the
disasters will swoop you out of this world.
Isn't that right, brothers and sisters?
So it's very, very important, brothers and
sisters.
We got to focus in the word of God.
Because if you do not accept, what is the
Lord Jesus going to say?
Many will say to me in that day, Lord,
Lord, have we not prophesied in your name?
And in your name have cast out devils?
And in your name have done many wonderful
works?
And then will I profess to them?
He's going to say, I don't know you.
Depart from me, you that work iniquity.
Sister Annie, we're almost done.
Less than 10 minutes and we will be done.
Okay, my dear sister, less than 10
minutes.
Brothers and sisters, final passage for
tonight.
All right, final passage for tonight.
What are the consequences of not keeping
up with God's judgment work?
Last one for tonight.
Okay, here we go.
Let's listen carefully.
The work of judgment is God's own work.
So it must naturally be carried out by God
himself.
It cannot be done by man in his stead.
Because judgment is the use of the truth
to conquer humankind.
There is
no question that God would still appear in
the incarnate
image to perform this work among man.
That is to say, the work of judgment is
God's own work.
Christ of
the last days shall use the truth to teach
people across the
world and make all truths known to them.
This is God's work of judgment.
Many have a bad feeling about the second
incarnation of God, for people find it
difficult to believe that God would become
flesh to do the work of judgment.
Nevertheless, I must tell you that the
work of God often goes far beyond the
expectations of man and is difficult for
human minds to accept.
God's work has an unstoppable momentum.
He
will not repeat the work of judgment again
just
because of the contribution you have made.
And you will be overcome with regret.
At letting such a good opportunity slip
by.
If you do not
believe my words, then just wait for that
great white throne
in the sky to pass judgment upon you.
You must know that all of the Israelites
spurned and denied Jesus.
And
yet the fact of Jesus' redemption of
mankind
still extended throughout the universe.
And to the ends of the earth.
Isn't this a reality that God made long
ago?
If you are still
waiting for Jesus to take you up to heaven,
then I say that
you are an obstinate piece of dead wood.
Jesus will not
acknowledge a false believer such as you,
who is disloyal
to the truth and seeks only blessings.
On the contrary,
He will show no mercy in casting you into
the lake of fire
to burn for tens of thousands of years.
Wow.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Amen.
So we could see how important God's work
of judgment really is, right?
So
with that being said, brothers and sisters,
I've
got a review question before we go, okay?
Review question.
I want to see how much you have understood
in tonight's topic.
And my question for everyone who is still
here is this.
Why does God come back to carry out the
work of judgment?
What needs to happen to our sins before we
can actually enter God's kingdom?
What do you think, Brother Jeff?
Brother Abraham?
Kenneth?
What do you think?
Bot?
Bot, what do you think?
Alex?
Jasmine?
Akunz?
Lisa?
Steve?
And Samuel?
Sister May?
Kim?
Sisley?
Annie?
Monica?
Liza?
Annette?
Edgar?
Elaine?
Rose?
Patricia?
And Miriam?
I think these are all the brothers and
sisters that are here.
What do you think, brothers and sisters?
Ooh, Jasmine hit the nail right on the
head again, sister.
Good sharing.
What about others?
What is the correct answer?
Sister Kim, not necessarily.
Remember, Sister Kim, we already do that
for the redemption.
We're talking about the judgment now,
Sister Kim, which is far deeper than just
asking for forgiveness.
We already do that.
We've been doing that for 2,000 years.
All right, you can try again, Sister Kim.
Amen, Brother Edgar.
Amen, amen.
What about Sister Annette?
Alex?
Bot?
Patricia?
And Rose?
You can try again, Brother Alex,
because God still has work to do, okay?
There's still work to do, my dear brother.
Amen, Sister Annie.
Good sharing.
Good sharing, Sister Annie.
Anyone else?
I see Sister Annette is typing.
Rose is typing.
What about Bot and Alex?
You can try again, okay, Alex?
What do you think?
Amen, Sister Rose.
Good sharing.
So Sister Annette, purify is right.
But give others... not give others a
chance.
Giving us a chance, Sister.
It's about you.
Judgment begins at the house of God.
It begins with the believers, right?
Meaning us a chance.
Not others.
Us.
Because God comes back to work in us.
Yes, exactly.
Amen, Sister Kim.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Let me send you the answer, okay?
How does God do the work of judgment?
Christ returns in the flesh to speak words
that reveal our sinful nature to purify us.
It's about the purification, okay,
brothers and sisters?
It's all about the purification.
Praise be to God.
So,
my dear brothers and sisters, I do want
to
invite you to come back tomorrow again.
It's going to be day three.
Day three.
And we're going
to talk about God's love for humanity and
how God has been
working from the beginning up until today.
All right?
We're going to talk about God's work,
how he has been working from the beginning
up until today, okay, brothers and
sisters?
I think you're all going to enjoy it.
Because if you don't know anything about
the history of God's work, like how it all
started and how it's going and how it'll
end, then please, come tomorrow.
All right?
Because we're going to learn how God has
guided humanity step by step to live on
earth, how he has fought against Satan
step by step to save us from sin,
and from the creation of the world until
now.
What about the price that God has paid?
Because it's been 6,000 years,
brothers and sisters, yes.
God has been waiting for 6,000 years.
6,000 years of waiting, of patience,
of effort.
Would you like to know what kind of people
God wants to gain?
Would you like to know the destination
that God will bring them into?
Well, join us tomorrow, okay?
Join us tomorrow, my beloved brothers and
sisters, and we'll know more of God's work.
We'll understand how he actually does it.
And you'll know how he has carried out
three stages of work.
Okay, brothers and sisters?
So who's going to join us tomorrow night
again?
Are you coming back tomorrow night again,
brothers and sisters?
Yes, no, maybe so?
I hope so.
Amen, amen, brothers and sisters.
Me too, me too.
I'll be here as well.
Praise be to God.
All right, praise be to God, brothers and
sisters.
I'll be here with you too, okay?
So after
the fellowship is done, if I didn't get a
chance to speak
with you today, then I'll call you today.
So there are
some brothers and sisters that I never got
a chance to speak
with, like Alex and Vata, and who else?
Some other brothers and sisters I never
got a chance to speak with.
So I'll definitely call you guys tonight.
If I already spoke with you, then
I'll just give you a call tomorrow, okay?
So with that being said, brothers and
sisters, let's quiet our hearts,
and let's give thanks.
Oh, Sister Annette, yes, I need to call
you too.
You're right, you're right, Sister.
And Annie, I need to call you too,
Sister Annie. Okay?
Amen! And Rose and Rose as well.
And Kenneth as well.
And Jasmine as well.
Wow.
Okay.
So let's do a quick prayer here together.
Amen.
Dear Almighty
God, Father God, we thank you so much for
another very
touching topic about your judgment work.
Dear God, we could see how much of the
truth we don't understand.
Dear Lord, we could tell that there's so
much work to be done in the last days.
You need to open a sealed book,
dear God.
And this sealed book has always been
prophesied in the Bible.
It's
just the fact that many of us, we don't
really
go quite deep into the truth, dear God.
And that's why we're here.
We're here to seek the truth, dear God,
so that we can comprehend your work,
so we can be prepared to welcome your
return.
So
we thank you for this online fellowship
that
you have prepared for all of us, dear God.
And I pray that we can leave this
fellowship with more knowledge.
Than what we did coming into it.
So dear Lord, we pray that we can come
back tomorrow, continue to give our whole
heart
to you and continue learning so that we
can
be protected by you in the great disasters.
Dear Lord, we thank you for all that you
do for each and every single one of us.
And we just want to give you all the
praise, all the honor and all the glory in
your precious, righteous, holy name,
Jesus Christ, we pray.
Amen.
Amen, brothers and sisters.
Thanks be to God.
All right, my dear brothers and sisters.
I'll talk to you guys very soon.
Okay.
I'll give you guys a call, very,
very soon.
Amen. Amen
Goodnight everyone.
Goodnight for now.
Goodnight
for now, I'll chat with you very soon,
okay, Annett
and Annie and Bott and Alex and Jasmine.
I'll talk to you guys very soon. Okay?
Amen.
God bless you all.